## Matthew Orellana

Strategist
WE Communications Australia
matthewjo19@hotmail.com
https://www.linkedin.com/in/matthew-o-6942761a2/

As a Brand Strategist, I engage with clients across multiple industry verticles to redefine their voices and achieve their strategic business outcomes. I am passionate about inclusive creativity and engaging with diverse voices to reflect real-world & tangible audience experiences. With almost three years sector experience, I work across brand and communications strategy, customer experience, digital media engagement, and community and stakeholder relations. I hold a Masters of Strategic Public Relations from the University of Sydney, where I gained valuable knowledge within media relations, crisis management, marketing and research theory, and campaign planning. As a Brand Strategist, I engage with clients across multiple industry verticles to redefine their voices and achieve their strategic business outcomes. I am passionate about inclusive creativity and engaging with diverse voices to reflect real-world & tangible audience experiences. With almost three years sector experience, I work across brand and communications strategy, customer experience, digital media engagement, and community and stakeholder relations. I hold a Masters of Strategic Public Relations from the University of Sydney, where I gained valuable knowledge within media relations, crisis management, marketing and research theory, and campaign planning. …see more

## Skills

Patient Engagement, Social Listening

## **Employment**

WE Communications Australia -

Brand Strategist	01/09/2023 - 01/01/2024
Junior Brand Strategist	01/01/2022 - 01/09/2023
Red Havas AU Social Media Assistant	01/11/2021 - 01/02/2022
Westpac Group Creative Strategy Assistant	01/07/2021 - 01/01/2022
Roselea Student Care Centre Senior Educator	01/12/2017 - 01/09/2021
Liquid Ideas Public Relations Intern	01/05/2021 - 01/07/2021

## Education

University of Sydney Masters of Strategic Public

Relations

University of Sydney Bachelor of Political